

Trnovska ulica 6, 1000 Ljubljana, Slovenia +386 41 389 099 novakmark9@gmail.com novakmark.co

Novak Mark, Front-End Developer & Web Designer

I am a positive and ambitious person, eager to learn and cope with new challenges. I'm passionate about creating the web a better place with two years plus of industry experience in designing web and one year as a dev. I am able to work well both in a team environment as well as using my own initiative.

Skills

- . HTML, CSS, JS, React, Next, Tailwind
- Teamwork, communication

- UI UX Design principles and rules, Adobe Suite
- · Problem solving, creativity, precision

Experience

Freelance designer and dev

2021 -

- Collaborating with creative teams on development of branding concepts, product ideas and design support.
- Designing and developing sites for smaller companies and startups using React, Next, rarely Wordpress.
- Partnered at .raw as a lead UI designer 2021-2022.

Product designer and developer Alumnio d.o.o.

dec 2020 - oct 2022

- Part of a start-up team of entrepreneurs and product developers.
- Worked on the brand image, product design, practiced design thinking.
- Designed, developed and maintained the website.
- Won two international prizes in less than 6 months.

Designer and event coordinator Nowa d.o.o.

2018 - 2021

- Delivered custom promotion materials for companies such as Spar, Hervis, OMW, Continental,...
- Collaborated with internal marketing teams and external printing companies to coordinate the designs, establish what kind of materials to make and strategy plans how to use them.
- Marketing events coordination, managing micro locations for promotion materials.

Education

Faculty of Design

2019-2023 (bachelor thesis on UI UX defense in September)

Faculty of Architecture (FAUL)

2015-201

Gimnazija Jožeta Plečnika Ljubljana

2011-201

Additional info

Languages

- English C1
- German B2
- Basic Spanish

Interests

- Web (FE development, creative development)
- UI UX
- Brand engineering